Hello, I'm a scribe.
Today, I'm before part of the public recording of the Ebichu Broadcasting Club,
I don't know why, but Yuna Kunisaki, Nonaka Kazami, and Yuna Nakamura are going bungee jumping,
I was wondering what was going on and what kind of nerve they had,
I'm not sure why, but Yuko Kunisaki, Nonaka Kazami, and Yuzo Nakamura are going to jump the bungee, and I'm wondering what kind of nerves they have.
So, I'll leave you to it.
Please tell us about your enthusiasm for bungee jumping.
Since I was born and said I was going to jump the bungee, I am going to jump the bungee properly and break out of my shell without waiting for an hour.
I won't wait an hour.
I can't wait an hour.
Good luck.
Hang in there.
You said you wanted to jump from high places this year,
I'll be ashamed if I don't do it even though this is my chance to do it.
I will do my best from this year.
I flew in New Zealand, so I thought I could do it.
I can only run 2 cm.
I jumped from 2 meters.
I jumped from about 2 meters, so I am sure I can do it.
I will do my best.
Yes, I was wondering if I could fly with a lunge.
Yes, um, run.
Yes, sir.
I was told that those under 18 years of age can only ride with the consent of a parent or guardian.
I've come all the way here to get a fluffy microphone for you, but...
But this time, I'm going to jump because I'm an adult again.
But this time, I'm going to jump again because I'm an adult now.
Two people...
Three.
Two.
Three. Sorry.
Two would like to give it a shot.
Good luck!
I'll do my best.
I'll go with you.
What do you say?
Looks delicious.
Looks so good!
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Oh, it's the next room.
Yuna Yuna, I'm about to tell you that the bungee didn't work.
What is it? This is
It's a free ball.
Harry Ball?
Crazy.
It's a falling ball.
Yuna Yuna rides it.
Yuna Yuna is a little bit scared.
But she rode it.
That's right.
It's going up a little bit.
If I wave, will you wave back?
I don't want to do anything I don't have to. Just wave back.
You're scaring him.
It's because you're cold.
You look like you're pouting.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay, we're all done here.
Okay, good luck.
All of you.
But it's a bit unexpected.
Hey, it's not that easy to find Mizuki's name, but...
Ah~
Bye-bye!
Yuna-san...
Yuna.
We have knocked on the safety mando and will check the point seat
Bye-bye.
bye bye bye
Bye-bye!
Oh no!
I can't stop looking at it.
Oh, no!
I'm scared!
I'll go up a little.
Chop-chop!
Huuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhu
Huuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhuuhu.
Tonme-chan...
Ok Jings, let's get started!
Head, please listen to that Tai USW firmly!
Let's start the countdown!
Oh, yeah.
Three, two, one.
Aaaaahhh...
Oh no!
No way!
No!
I'm scared!
Oh, my God!
Look, look, look!
Oh, here it comes!
Butt!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yes, we're all done around here once you unbuckle your belts.
Please enjoy your ride.
Thank you very much.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
A-ha-ha-ha!
Thank you for watching.
I was louder than you.
How was it?
It was scary, really scary.
I really thought my heart was going to jump out of my chest, but it was super scary.
I was really loud. I was...
It was great. It was great.
I was on something.
"Why are you doing that? I was like, "Why are you doing that?
With my feet.
He's not talking anymore.
I was saying bye-bye to Red with my foot.
And he said, "Why are you doing that? And all of a sudden he got mad at me.
And I closed my eyes and it was over.
I was so scared.
I was suddenly angry with Yuna-san.
Enjoy the next time!
Also, I heard that Yuna Yuna is going to ride her second one.
I heard that this one is a little bit different from the other one, so...
Are you sure you don't want to ride with me?
Emma.
I don't mind if you ride with Noka.
Whoever loses in rock-paper-scissors, let's ride together.
What's this like?
It's a fall.
Falling down?
It's almost like a roller coaster.
Before the roller coaster, you either move or you don't.
Are you up for a ride?
Let's ride it together.
Mr. Nonoka seems a little shaken up.
Okay, Nonoka, let's ride together.
Yes!
That's what I thought.
Only one more to go.
Wow.
Okay, I'm going to go downstairs and I'm going to say "yelp.
I can't hear you.
Hey, I'm scared my ass is shaking.
I just said my butt is shaking.
I'm scared.
I didn't go to that thing.
Oh, my God!
What's happening?
My ass is shaking.
Oh, shit!
What the hell is that?
Is it worse than before?
My ass is shaking.
I can feel it.
What's with the butt tremor?
I don't think so.
Oh, no!
Mr. Nonaka's joining us now.
The three of us are going.
Good luck!
He looks even scarier than before.
You're trembling.
He's got a big smile on his face.
Oh, no!
Please do your best!
Go for it!
I'll do my best!
Playlist will start shortly!
Go ahead and pull it!
I'm off!
Yuno-chan is amazing.
Yay!
Woooo!
Why are you doing this!
Wait a minute!
Coming!
Three, two, one! Bungy!
Once the thing has acquired a belt.
Please raise your safety caps and step out.
As the center of the belly
Press the red button to release.
Please be careful
I'm in.
It's not flying.
I'm off!
Mr. Naka was shouting, I could hear him.
How was it?
It was scary.
Yuna's face was dead from the start.
Maybe it'll work.
How was it?
When we decided to go to Yumeirando yesterday.
I was really looking forward to this.
But it's so scary when you're near Eezar.
That's why I'm in this cab.
I'm shivering at home.
How was the throat?
Yes, it was great.
I went there thinking I was going to fly in a bunch.
I thought I had to do something today.
I'm glad to hear that you were able to speak and hear so well!
The snow was beautiful.
I'm glad.
Yunasan looks relaxed.
I thought you were shouting.
But I looked for Tokyo Tower.
I couldn't find it.
I was like, "Who the hell is Tokyo Tower?
Thank goodness you're done.
Yay!
Okay, so...
Today I rode Crazy Cute instead of Bungy.
When I turn 18 again, I will come back to travel Bungy.
Okay, so that's it, you got me done with the closing?
You can finish too.
You can tighten up the most.
I'm glad I had this really valuable experience today.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye!